Guide to the Fairchild Camera and Instrument Corporation, Research and Development Division,Technical Reports and Progress Reports. 1965-1987
Department of Special Collections
Fairchild Camera and Instrument Corporation, Research and Development Division,Technical Reports and Progress Reports, 1965-1987.
M1055
Fairchild Camera and Instrument Corporation, Research and Development Division
11 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Arranged chronologically, the published listing includes authors of technical reports and dates of progress reports.
Administrative Information
Access
None.
Acquisition Information
Gift of National Semiconductor, 1988.
Collection Scope and Content Summary
Arranged chronologically, the published listing includes authors of technical reports and dates of progress reports.
Access Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Assimos, John A.; Barry, Michael L.; Baylis, D.; Bozarth, Joe.; Bravman, John.; Cagan, M.; Caplan, Philip J.; Crossley, P.A.; Deal, Bruce E.; Delfino, M.; Doshi, Pravin.; Duffek, Edward F.; Dumesnil, M.E.; Dyck, R.H.; Early, James M.; Farrier, M.G.; Feltham, Steve.; Fulks, R.T.; Hanson, D.; Hess, Dennis W.; Hushner, John D.; Iqbal, A.; Ishikawa, Robert.; Justi, Stefan.; Kamins, T.I.; Keyser, Thomas A.; Kim, Choong-ki.; Lawrence, John E.; Learn, Art J.; Lehrer, William I.; Leitner, P.; Lie, Liang N.; MacKenna, E.L.; Major, J.A.; Manolin, Juliana.; McDonald, R.C.; Meieran, Eugene.; Milgram, A.A.; Mruzik, Michael.; Neuman, Ralph.; Nowicki, R.S.; Oldberg, Ralph C.; Patel, Vikram.; Pierce, John M.; Plummer, James D.; Poindexter, Edward H.; Powell, R.A.; Pressaco, Sylvia.; Rabinovitch, Bernard.; Razouk, Reda R.; Reifsteck, T.A.; Sah, C.T.; Seeds, R.; Sklar, Maija.; Suaya, Roberto.; Thomas, M.E.; Townsend, S.; Venkateswaran, K.; Westphal, S.; Wong, Brian.; Yep, T.D.; Yu, A.Y.C.; Electronic industries.; Electronics--Research--United States.; Solid-state electronics.; Science--History.; Semiconductors.; Microelectronics industry--California--Santa Clara County.; Computer industry--United States.; Computer engineering.; Science and industry.
Collection Contents
- Sah, C.T. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Rabinovitch, Bernard; Ishikawa, Robert (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Seeds, R. (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Lawrence, John E. (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Dumesnil, M.E. (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Doshi, Pravin (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Meieran, Eugene (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Townsend, S. (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Yu, A.Y.C. (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Duffek, Edward F. (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Sklar, M. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Neuman, Ralph (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Kim, Choong-ki (Box 1, Folder 8)
- MacKenna, E.L. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Hess, Dennis (2 copies) (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Assimos, John A. (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Kamins, T.I. (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Deal, B.E. (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Olberg, Ralph; Bozarth, Joe (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Hess, D.W. (#630) (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Hess, D.W. (#631) (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Feltham, Steve (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Hess, D.W. (#633) (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Olberg, Ralph C. (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Nowicki, R.S. (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Deal, B.E.; Hess, D.W. (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Wong, Brian (Box 1, Folder 12)
- McDonald, R.C. (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Learn, Art (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Hess, D.W. (#640) (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Deal, B.E.; Hess, D.W. (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Olberg, R.C. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Hess, Dennis (#579) (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Learn, A.J.; Hess, D.W. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Hess, D.W.; Deal, B.E. (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Baylis, D. (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Deal, Bruce E. (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Deal, B.E.; Hess, D.W. (#587) (Box 2, Folder 3)
- McDonald, R.C. (#643) (Box 2, Folder 4)
- McDonald, R.C. (#646) (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Pierce, John M. (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Deal, Bruce E. (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Pierce, John M. (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Deal, Bruce E.; Early, James M. (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Deal, B.E. (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Razouk, Reda R.; Deal, Bruce E. (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Crossley, P.A. (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Lehrer, William I. (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Caplan, Philip J.; Poindexter, Edward H.; Deal, Bruce E.; Razouk, Reda R. (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Deal, Bruce E. (#594) (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Hasher, John D. (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Delfino, M. (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Deal, Bruce E.; Plummer, James D. (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Deal, Bruce E. (#597) (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Deal, Bruce E. (#651A) (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Mruzik, Michael R.; Suaya, Roberto (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Keyser, Thomas; Pierce, John (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Thomas, M.E.; Pierce, J.M. (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Delfino, M. (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Justi, Stefan; Bravman, John (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Delfino, M. (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Delfino, M.; Razouk (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Poindexter, Edward H.; Caplan, Philip J.; Deal, Bruce E.; Razouk, Reda R. (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Farrier, M.G.; Dyck, R.H. (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Delfino, M. (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Delfino, M.; Lehrer, W.I. (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Sklar, Maija (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Deal, B.E.; Crossley, P.A. (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Razouk, Reda R.; Lie, Liang N.; Deal, Bruce E. (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Lehrer, W.I.; Pierce, J.M. (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Husher, John D. (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Venkateswaran, K. (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Delfino, M.; Reifsteck, T.A.; Lie, L.N. (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Cagan, M. (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Pierce, J.M.; Thomas, M.E. (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Delfino, M.; Razouk, R.R. (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Patel, Vikram (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Delfino, M.; Reifstock (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Westphal, S.; Razouk (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Razouk, R.R.; Delfino, M.; Fulks, R.T.; Powell, R.A.; Yep, T.D. (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Milgram, A.A. (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Delfino, M. (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Lie, L.N.; Razouk, R.R. (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Milgram, A.A. (#671) (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Milgram, A.A. (#672) (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Iqbal, A. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Deal, Bruce E.; Barry, Michael L. (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Milgram, A. (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Cagan, M.R.; Keyser, T. (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Cagan, M.; Leitner, P. (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Hanson, D.; Keyser, T.; Pierce, T. (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Delfino, M.; Reifsteck (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Cagan, M.R.; Major, J.A. (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Deal, Bruce E.; Manoliu, Juliana; Westphal, Sylvia L. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Milgram, A. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Milgram, A.A. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Pressacco, Sylvia L.; Razouk, Reda R. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Pierce, J.M.; Thomas, M.E.; Keyser, T.; Cagan, M.; Leitner, P. (Box 4, Folder 8)
- A Solid State of Progress (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Moore, G.E. Oct. 1, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Moore, Gordon. Jan. 1, 1960: Chemistry Sect. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Moore, Gordon. Jan. 1, 1960: Physics Sect. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Moore, G.E. Feb. 1, 1960: Chemistry Sect. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Moore, G.E. Feb. 1, 1960: Physics Sect. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Sello, H. Feb. 1, 1960: Preproduction Sect. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Moore, G.E. Mar. 1, 1960: Preproduction Sect. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Moore, G.E. Mar. 1, 1960: Physics Sect. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Moore, G.E. Apr. 1, 1960: Reliability Evaluation Div. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Moore, G.E. Apr. 1, 1960: Chemistry Sect. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Moore, G.E. Apr. 1, 1960: Physics Sect. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Grinich, V.H. Apr. 13, 1960: Engin. Dept. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Moore, G. May 1, 1960: Chem. Sect. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Moore, G. May 1, 1960: Physics Sect. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Moore, G. June 1, 1960: Library Rep. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Moore, G. June 1, 1960: Physics Sect. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Moore, G. July 1, 1960: Chemistry Sect. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Moore, G. June1, 1960: Chemistry Sect. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Moore, G. July 1, 1960: Micrologic Section (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Moore, G. July 1, 1960: Transistor Devel. Sect. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Moore, G. July 1, 1960: Physics Sect. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Grinich, V.H. July 7, 1960: RAD Dept. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Grinich, V.H. Aug. 1, 1960: Transistor Devel. Sect. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Grinich, V.H. Aug. 1, 1960: Physics Sect. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Grinich, V.H. Sep. 1, 1960: Micrologic Sect. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Grinich, V.H. Aug. 1, 1960: Chemistry Sect. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Grinich, V.H. Aug. 1, 1960: Micrologic Sect. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Grinich, V.H. Sep. 1, 1960: Chemistry Sect. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Grinich, V.H. Sep. 1, 1960: Physics Sect. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Grinich, V.H. Sep. 1, 1960: Transistor Devel. Sect. Moore, G.E. Sep. 16, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Grinich, V.H. Oct. 1, 1960: Transistor Devel. Sect. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Grinich, V.H. Oct. 1, 1960: Chemistry Sect. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Oct. 1, 1960: Physics Sect. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Oct. 1, 1960: Micrologic Sect. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Nov. 1, 1960: Chemistry Sect. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Nov. 1, 1960: Transistor Devel. Sect. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Nov. 1, 1960: Micrologic Sect. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Nov. 1, 1960: Physics Sect. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Moore, Gordon E. Nov. 7, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Norman, Robert H. Nov. 30, 1960: Device Eval. Sect. (2 copies) (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Kleiner, Eugene. Dec. 1, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Dec. 1, 1960: Chemistry Sect. (4 copies) (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Dec. 1, 1960: Electro-Optical Devices Sect. (2 copies) (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Dec. 1, 1960: Materials Sect. (C.S. Roberts; 2 copies) (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Dec. 1, 1960: Micrologic Sect. (4 copies) (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Dec. 1, 1960: Physics Sect. (4 copies) (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Dec. 1, 1960: Transistor Devel.Sect. (4 copies) (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Dec. 2, 1960: Applications Engineering Sect. (Shultz, Robert H.; 2 copies) (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Norman, Robert H. Dec. 31, 1960: Device Eval. Sect. (2 copies) (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Jan. 1, 1961: Chemistry Sect. (2 copies) (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Jan. 1, 1961: Electro-Optical Dev. (4 copies) (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Jan. 1, 1961: Materials Sect. (2 copies) (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Jan. 1, 1961: Micrologic Sect. (2 copies) (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Jan. 1, 1961: Physics Sect. (2 copies) (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Jan. 1, 1961: Transistor Devel. Sect. (2 copies) (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Jan. 3, 1961: Applications Engin. Sect. (2 copies) (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Jan. 9, 1961: Moore, G.E.; Grinich, V.H. (2 copies) (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Jan. 15, 1961: Moore, G.E.; Grinich V.H. (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Jan. 31, 1961: Device Eval. Sect. (2 copies) (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Feb. 1, 1961: Chemistry Sect. (2 copies) (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Feb. 1, 1961: Electro-Optical Devices sect. (2 copies) (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Feb. 1, 1961: Materials Sect. (2 copies) (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Feb. 1, 1961: Micrologic Sect. (2 copies) (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Feb. 1, 1961: Physics Sect. (2 copies) (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Feb. 1, 1961: Transistor Devel. Sect. (2 copies) (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Feb. 6, 1961: Applic.Engin. Sect. (2 copies) (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Feb. 8, 1961: Moore, G.E.; Grinich, V.H. (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Feb. 28, 1961: Device Eval. Sect.(2 copies (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Mar. 1 1961: Chemistry Sect. (2 copies) (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Mar. 1 1961: Electro-Optical Dev. (2 copies) (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Mar. 1 1961: Materials Sect. (2 copies) (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Mar. 1 1961: Micrologic Sect. (2 copies) (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Mar. 1 1961: Physics Sect. (2 copies) (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Mar. 1 1961: Transistor Devel. Sect. (2 copies) (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Mar. 3 1961: Applications Engin. Sect. (2 copies) (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Mar. 8, 1961: Moore, G.E.; Grinich, V.H. (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Mar. 31, 1961: Device Eval. Sect. (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Mar. 31, 1961: Transducer Sect. (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Mar. 31, 1961: Transducer Devel. Sect. (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Apr. 1, 1961: Chemistry Sect. (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Apr. 1, 1961: Microelectronics Research Sect. (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Apr. 1, 1961: Device Development Sect. (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Apr. 1, 1961: Physics Sect. (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Apr. 3, 1961: Applications Engineering Sect. (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Apr. 11, 1961: Moore, G.E.; Grinich, V.H. (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Apr. 30, 1961: Device Eval. Sect. (3) (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Apr. 30, 1961 - May 1, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- May 10, 1961 - June 30, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- July 1, 1961 - Aug. 1, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Aug. 11, 1961 - Sep. 30, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Sep. 30, 1961 - Oct. 31, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Nov. 1, 1961 - Dec.12, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Jan. 1, 1962 - Feb. 1, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Feb. 9, 1962 - Mar. 30, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Apr. 1, 1962 - May 1, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- May 2, 1962 - June 30, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- July 1, 1962 - Aug. 9, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Jan. 15, 1963 - Feb. 1, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Feb. 4, 1963 - Mar. 5, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Apr. 1, 1963 - Apr. 4, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- June 1, 1963 - July 1, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Aug. 1, 1963 - Sep. 1, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Oct. 1, 1963 - Nov. 4, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Chemistry Section File, May - Aug. 1963 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Chemistry Section File, Sep. - Dec. 1963 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Jan. 1, 1964 - Feb. 1, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Feb. 4, 1964 - Mar. 4, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Apr. 1, 1964 - Apr. 3, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- May 1, 1964 - May 6, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- June 1, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- July 1, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Aug. 1, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Sep. 1, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Oct. 1, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Oct. 6, 1964 - Nov. 1, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Nov. 3, 1964 - Dec. 1, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Jan. 1, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Feb. 1, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Mar. 1, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Mar. 31, 1965 - Apr. 1, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Apr. 30, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- May 1, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- June 1, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- July 1,1965 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Aug. 1965 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Sep. 1965 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Oct. 1965 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Nov. 1965 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Dec. 1965 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Jan. 1966 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Jan. 1, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Feb. - Mar. 1966 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Apr. 1966 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- May 1966 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- June 1966 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- July 1966 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Aug. 1966 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Sep. 1966 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Oct. - Nov. 1966 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Dec. 1966 - Jan. 1967 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Feb. - Mar. 1967 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Apr. - May 1967 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- June - July 1967 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Aug. - Sep. 1967 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Oct. - Nov. 1967 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Dec. 1967 - Jan. 1968 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Feb. - Apr. 1968 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- May 1968 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- June - July, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Aug. - Sep. 1968 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Oct. - Nov. 1968 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Dec. 1968 - Jan. 1969 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Feb. - Mar. 1969 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Apr. - May 1969 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- June - July 1969 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Aug. - Sep. 1969 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Oct. 1969 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Nov. 1969 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Dec. 1969 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Feb. 1970 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Feb. 1970 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Mar. 1970 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Apr. 1970 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- May 1970 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- June 1970 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- July 1970 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Aug. 1970 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Sep. 1970 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Oct. 1970 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Nov. 1970 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Dec. 1970 - Jan. 1971 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Feb. 1971 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Mar. - Apr. 1971 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- May - June 1971 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- July - Aug. 1971 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Sep. 1971 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Nov. - Dec. - 1971 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Jan. - Mar. 1972 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Apr. - Aug. 1972 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Sep. 1972 - Feb. 1973 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Mar. 1973 - Oct. 1973 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Nov. 1973 - Feb. 1974 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Mar. - May 1974 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- June - Oct. 1974 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Nov. 1974 - Apr. 1975 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- May - Nov. 1975 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Dec. 1975 - July 1976 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Aug. 1976 - April 1977 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- May - Nov. 1977 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Dec. 1977 - May 1978 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- June - Dec. 1978 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Jan. - June 1979 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- July - Nov. 1979 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Dec. 1979 - Mar. 1980 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Apr. - Aug. 1980 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Sep. - Dec. 1980 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Jan. - Apr. 1981 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- May - Aug. 1981 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Sep. - Nov. 1981 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Dec. 1981 - Mar. 1982 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Apr. - June 1982 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- July - Aug. 1982 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Sep. - Oct. 1982 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Nov. 1982 - Feb. 1983 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Mar. - May 1983 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- June - Sep. 1983 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Oct. 1983 - April 1984 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- May - Dec. 1984 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Jan. - Mar. 1985 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Apr. - May 1985 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- June - July 1985 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Aug. - Oct. 1985 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Nov. 1985 - Jan. 1986 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Feb. - Apr. 1986 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- May - June 1986 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- July - Sep. 1986 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Oct. - Dec. 1986 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Jan. - Feb. 1987 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Mar. - Apr. 1987 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- May - June 1987 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Aug. - Oct. 1987 (Box 22, Folder 7)